Nicholas Lombardo

238 Fairmount Ave Philadelphia, PA 19010 (610) 247-2464 Lombardo 15@temple.edu

A high-energy, confident professional with enthusiasm for driving sales in a fast-paced environment. Strength in bridging cultural gaps among people through education and interpersonal relationships. Demonstrates accomplishment of goals through ability to deliver experiences, oversee assignments from conception to completion and seamless event management.

Experience

2017-Present

SCHULSON COLLECTIVE (Independence Beer Garden)-Bartender

- Maintained inventory of bar products, including alcohol and supplies to ensure high volume of daily and weekly sales
- Created a welcoming environment for visiting guests providing a memorable experience
- Demonstrated flexibility in regard to work assignments and work schedule

2018

RENT SCENE- Lead Generator/Team Member

- Qualified leads of potential clients throughout the Philadelphia area
- Managed the application process from start to finish, coordinate apartment tours, a provide all pricing to make sure clients get the best possible deal
- Step by step guidance to finding clients an apartment
- Demonstrated the ability to multi-task at a fast pace while dealing with various situations/individuals

2016-2017 Angeles, CA

UCLA -Assistant to the Director of Performance Nutrition

Responsible for providing student athletes with proper nutrition for performance and recovery, to meet body composition goals, as well as performance objectives throughout the collegiate season.

- Maintained weekly inventory including BODPOD tests and nutrition education development tasks for athletes
- Collaborated with the Sports RD to facilitate education sessions for Olympic sport teams
- Provided student-athletes with nutrition recovery and body composition goals
- Organized and managed deliveries for the Director and teams
- Analyze nutritional tactics to help improve performance and recovery methods across the sports teams

2015-2016 **Nutrition Unlimited** – *Office Manager* Philadelphia, PA

Assisted thirteen Registered Dietitians across a multitude of locations around the Philadelphia region.

- Promoted and sold the Nutrition Unlimited brand to new clients such as the Philadelphia Fire Department and Independence Blue Cross
- Interacted daily with various clients and companies
- Managed over 500 client accounts at 12 locations in the Philadelphia area
- Tracked patients statistics including blood work, weight loss, and dietary changes for all locations
- Provided extensive billing and managed company expenses

Education

2019

Penn LPS Coding Bootcamp

• 24 week front-end development program. HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Express.js, Node.js

2011-2016 **Temple University, College of Health Professionals** Philadelphia, PA

- Bachelor of Science in Kinesiology (Concentration Pre-Health)
- Member of The Exercise Science Association
- Participant in Temple University Powerlifting club

Skills & Certifications

- Skills: Excel, PowerPoint, Microsoft Office, SharePoint, Data Analysis
- Member: The Exercise Science Association of Temple University 2013-2016
- Member: Power lifting Club Temple University 2013-2015
- Certified in USA Weightlifting- Level 1 Sports Performance Coach February, 2014